behindthevoiceactors.com 2019-05-19

# Privacy Policy | Behind The Voice Actors

**EFFECTIVE DATE** : October 28, 2013 

Your privacy is important to us. If you have any questions about this Policy, contact us at <https://www.behindthevoiceactors.com/contact/> or email us at team [@] behindthevoiceactors.com. 

**1\. What's Covered Under this Privacy Policy:**

1.1 This policy applies to all of the services offered by Inyxception Enterprises, Inc. DBA Behind The Voice Actors ("BTVA", "We", "Us", "Ours"). 

1.2 This policy covers how We treat personal information that We collect and receive. Personal information is any information about you that is personally identifiable (like your email address), and that is not commonly, publicly available. 

1.3 This policy does not apply to practices of companies that are not owned or controlled by Us. 

**2\. Information: Collection & Usage **

2.1 BTVA operates and is hosted in the United States and, depending on your country of residence, the submission of personally identifiable information to our sites may involve some transfer of personal information to the United States. You understand and consent to having any personal information you provide transferred to and processed in the United States. You should be aware that privacy laws in the United States may not provide protections equivalent to those of your country of residence. 

2.2 Several of the services that we offer require registration as a condition of use. We collect personal information when you register with BTVA. 

2.3 When you register, we may ask for information such as your username, email address, date of birth, and personal interests. When you register with BTVA and sign in to our service, you are not anonymous to us. 

2.4 BTVA may use the personal information for the purposes described in section 3 below, as well as: 

(i) Customizing the advertising and content you see;   
(ii) Auditing, research, and analysis to maintain, protect, and improve our services;  
(iii) Ensuring the technical functioning of our network;  
(iv) Fulfilling your requests for products and services, including the development of new services;  
(v) Contacting you;  
(vi) Conducting research; and  
(vii) Provide anonymous reporting for clients. 

2.5 We automatically receive and record information on our server logs, including your IP address, the web request, and one or more cookies which may uniquely identify your browser. These server logs may also include your browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request. 

2.6 **Cookies** : A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your browser. 

(i) When you visit BTVA, we may set and access cookies on your computer;  
(ii) If your browser is set to refuse all cookies, some features of our site may not function properly;  
(iii) We use cookies to improve the quality of our services by storing user preferences and tracking user trends;  
(iv) Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on our site send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. We have no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

2.7 When you send email or other communication to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests, and improve our services. 

2.8 We may present links in a format that enables us to track when the links are followed. We may use this information to improve the quality of our content and advertising. 

2.9 Contests, Promotions and Sweepstakes:   
From time to time, we may host a contest, promotion or sweepstake on the site. You may be asked to provide personal information or permit the transfer to a third party of your personal information in connection with such contest, promotion or sweepstake. It will be disclosed at the point of collection or transfer who is collecting or transferring the information and whose privacy statement applies, and it will be your choice whether or not you wish to permit such transfer or collection of personal information to a third party. 

2.10 Retention of Information.  
We retain information for as long as required, allowed or we believe it useful, but do not undertake retention obligations. We may dispose of information in our discretion without notice, subject to applicable law that specifically requires the handling or retention of information. You must keep your own, separate back-up records. 

2.11 Advertising  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp 

2.12 Advertising Privacy Statement  
This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (â€œAdThriveâ€) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site. AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies. 

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies. 

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: https://adssettings.google.com. You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative's multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: http://optout.networkadvertising.org. However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. 

For European Economic Area Residents 

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can [contact us here](https://www.behindthevoiceactors.com/contact/) and contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences icon. (Available in the EU.) 

**3\. Links to Other Sites**

3.1 BTVA's site may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different from ours. We do not have control over the information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. You should consult the privacy policy of these other sites to learn how your privacy is protected. 

**4\. Disclosure and Use of Personal Information**

4.1 BTVA processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this policy or any other applicable service-specific privacy notice. We retain the right to review our data collection, storage, and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store, and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but it is incumbent upon our users so update and/or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

4.2 Children:  
BTVA's site is not intended for use by children, especially those under 14. No one under age 13 should provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas and forums. 

4.3 Disclosing Personal Information: 

(i) We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or companies except when we have your permission.   
(ii) Notwithstanding the above, if we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary, we may share your personal information under the following circumstances: 

(a) To satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request (which may include, but is not limited to, responding to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or establishing or exercising our legal rights or defending against legal claims);  
(b) To enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof;  
(c) To detect, prevent, investigate, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or  
(d) To protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of BTVA, its users, or the public, as required or permitted by law. 

(iii) We may share certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information with third parties (such as number of users who click on a particular advertisement), but that information shall not identify you individually.  
(iv) If BTVA becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of any or all of its assets, we will provide notice to you before your personal information is transferred and may become subject to a different privacy policy. 

4.4 Using Personal Information: 

(i) BTVA may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet such targeting criteria (such as, males aged 18-24 in a particular geographic area).  
(ii) We do not provide any personal information to an advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad, however, by interacting with or viewing the ad, you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 

4.5 Information Security; Confidentiality 

(i) We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to and/or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of data. These include (but may not be limited to): 

(a) Internal reviews of our data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures; and  
(b) Measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.  

(ii) We believe we use reasonable precautions to keep the personal information you disclose to our websites secure. However, we cannot guarantee there will not be a breach and we are not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of any third parties.  
(iii) You must protect against unauthorized access to your username and password, and to your computer. Please sign off when finished using a shared computer. Your emails to us are not necessarily secure against interception so do not include sensitive information in them. We generally will not ask for passwords in an email and you should assume that if you get such a request, it might be fraudulent. YOU MUST DO WHAT YOU REASONABLY CAN TO ENSURE THE SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.  
(iv) Please note that BTVA is not responsible for the information you volunteer about yourself in the discussions in our forums, comments, or other publicly accessible interaction, or information that you choose to make public in your member profile or other areas that allow users to upload or post content. We discourage users from posting personally identifiable information in this fashion, and any personally identifiable information you post to these areas is not covered by this Policy. 

4.6 Editing and Deleting Your Account Information 

(i) You can edit your account information at any time.  
(ii) You can delete your account by contacting us at <https://www.behindthevoiceactors.com/contact/> or contacting any Administrator listed [here](https://www.behindthevoiceactors.com/forums/faq.php?faq=vb3_board_faq#faq_adminsandmods). 

4.7 Changes to Policy 

(i) We reserve the right to update and/or change this policy from time to time.  
(ii) For any minor changes, will not reduce your rights without your explicit consent.  
(iii) For any major or significant changes which do not reduce your rights and therefore do not require explicit consent, we will place a prominent notice on our site.  
(iv) For any major or significant changes which require your consent, such as the way we treat your personal information, we will send a notice to the primary email address listed on your account. 

4.8 Questions and/or Suggestions  
If you have any question or concerns about this policy, please feel free to contact us at any time through this website. 

**

Your continued access to or use of our site shall be deemed your acceptance of the Privacy Policy.

Please visit our [Terms of Use](https://www.behindthevoiceactors.com/terms-of-use/) page for more information concerning your use of BTVA's website and other services. The Terms of Use are incorporated by reference into this Privacy Policy.

We recommend you to come back to this web page and review this Privacy Policy regularly so that you remain aware of the terms and conditions that apply to you.

**
